A Guide to the Booton Herndon Papers, 1939-1986
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Alphabetical Files (Box 1-53)
  - Outlines for Possible Books or Stories 1957-1967 (Box 34)
  - Over the Hump- Correspondence and Marketing 1961-1966, 2 folders (Box 35)
  - Parent's League 1956-1958 (Box 35)
  - Personal Correspondence 1943, 1962-1969 (Box 35)
  - Peterson, Dick 1958-1961, n.d. (Box 35)
  - Plum, Milt ca. 1961 (Box 35)
  - Poetry Research n.d. (Box 35)
  - Polzer, John 1955-1956 (Box 35)
  - Praised and Damned, The Story of Fulton Lewis, Jr.- Correspondence and Manuscript 1953-1956, 4 folders (Box 36)
  - Prep All Stars (football) 1956 (Box 36)
  - Prep All Stars Follow-up (football) 1956 (Box 36)
  - Prep School Applications 1965-1966 (Box 36)
  - Princeton University Conference 1959-1960 (Box 36)
  - Private Eyes n.d. (Box 36)
  - Public Relations 1968, 1970 (Box 36)
  - Public School (Desegregation in Virginia) 1958-1962 (Box 37)
  - Puller, Gen. Lewis "Chesty" 1963, n.d. (Box 37)
  - Quarterbacks 1951-1962 (Box 37)
  - Quinine & Arthur E. Fischer 1963-1964, n.d., 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Rackets for Redbook 1950-1953, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Randle, Sonny n.d. (Box 38)
  - Ray, Johnny 1952 (Box 38)
  - Red Run, Michigan - Pipeline Explosion, Cold Weather 1982 (Box 38)
  - Reed, James A.: Biographical Sketch ca. 1968 (Box 38)
  - Reed, James A.: Contract 1968 (Box 38)
  - Reed, James A.: Correspondence 1968, (1971-1972) (Box 38)
  - Reed, James A.: Expenses 1968 (Box 38)
  - The Speeches of James A. Reed Manuscript 1968, 3 folders (Box 38)
  - Restricted Clubs 1968 (Box 39)
  - Review Copies of Books - List of Recipients 1965, n.d. (Box 39)
  - Rickenbacker- Correspondence, Contract 1965-1969, n.d. (Box 39)
  - Rickenbacker- Reviews and Corrections 1967-1968, n.d. (Box 39)
  - Rocket Belt Research 1963-1968, n.d. (Box 39)
  - Rodgers, Cal 1957 (Box 39)
  - "Role Patterns" 1967 (Box 39)
  - St. Louis 1960 (Box 39)
  - St. Martin's Press - Contract 1962-1963 (Box 39)
  - Satisfaction Guaranteed- Reviews 1972-1973 (Box 39)
  - Scott, Marshal L. 1953-1954 (Box 39)
  - Seventh Avenue, N.Y. 1956 (Box 39)
  - Seventh Cavalry 1961-1962 (Box 39)
  - The Seventh Day: The Story of The Seventh-Day Adventists- Correspondence 1961-1968 (Box 40)
  - Shesta, John 1952 (Box 40)
  - Skin Diving 1955-1956, 1960 (Box 40)
  - Sky Diving 1960 (Box 40)
  - Slocum, Harvey 1952-1959, 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Small Business Investment Companies n.d. (Box 40)
  - Smith, Terry "Tiger" 1968 (Box 40)
  - Society of Magazine Writers 1955-1972, 5 folders (Box 41)
  - Speed Trap 1954-1956 (Box 41)
  - "Splendor in the Grass" - Correspondence and Manuscripts ca. 1947, ca. 1966, 2 folders (Box 41)
  - "Splendor in the Grass" - Correspondence and Manuscripts ca. 1966, 3 folders (Box 42)
  - Steelers 1954-1955 (Box 42)
  - Story Ideas 1961-1969, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Strategic Air Command (SAC) Wife 1959-1962 (Box 43)
  - Stutzer, Helen B. 1955 (Box 43)
  - "The Summer of the Blue Roadster" ca. 1959 (Box 43)
  - The Sweetest Music This Side of Heaven- Guy Lombardo 1955, 1964-1969, n.d. (Box 43)
  - Tarawa 1958 (Box 43)
  - Tatum, James 1956 (Box 43)
  - Tebell, Gus 1941, 1949, 1952-1954 (Box 43)
  - Teen-Age Driving 1952-1956 (Box 44)
  - "The Three Lives of Miss Minnie" - Correspondence, Research, Manuscript 1956 (Box 44)
  - They Made the World- Draft and Typed Manuscript n.d., 2 folders (Box 44)
  - Tobacco Research 1963-1967, n.d. (Box 44)
  - "Tough Ombres of the 90th Division" n.d. (Box 44)
  - Traitors 1960 (Box 44)
  - Travel - Correspondence re: Accomodations and Advertisements 1960-1962, n.d. (Box 45)
  - Treasury Department 1954-1956 (Box 45)
  - Tubex: Correspondence with Bernard Geis Associates, Inc., Publisher 1983-1986 (Box 45)
  - Tubex: Correspondence re: Research Material 1983-1984 (Box 45)
  - Tubex: Correspondence re: Split with Daniel N. Kuland 1985 (Box 45)
  - Tubex: Manuscript - Early Version n.d., 3 folders (Box 45)
  - Tubex: Manuscripts - Early Version 1985, n.d., 4 folders (Box 46)
  - Tubex: Manuscript - Corrected 1986 (Box 47)
  - Tubex: Manuscript - Late Version n.d., 3 copies (Box 47)
  - Tubex: Manuscript - Working Copy n.d., 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Tubex: Notes and Rough Drafts n.d. (Box 47)
  - Tubex: Outline, Correspondence with Geis 1983-1984 (Box 48)
  - Tubex: Research Material - Conversation with Dr. Greenwell 1978 (Box 48)
  - Tubex: Research Material - Exercise for Old Folks n.d. (Box 48)
  - Tubex: Research Material - Exercise for the Handicapped n.d. (Box 48)
  - Tubex: Research Material - Exercises with the Tube n.d. (Box 48)
  - Tubex: Research Material - Illustrations for Book 1984 (Box 48)
  - Tubex: Research Material - Notes from Dan Kuland 1984, 2 folders (Box 48)
  - Tubex: Research Material - Other Fitness Programs 1983-1984, n.d., 3 folders (Box 49)
  - Tubex: Research Material - Pamphlets, Newsletters re: Health and Exercise 1975-1978 (Box 49)
  - Tubex: Research Material - Weight Control n.d. (Box 49)
  - United Churchmen 1954 (Box 50)
  - The United States Forest Service 1955 (Box 50)
  - United States Information Agency 1956-1957, n.d. (Box 50)
  - The Unlikeliest Hero - The Story of Private Desmond T. Doss 1945-1969, n.d., 3 folders (Box 50)
  - Van Orden, George - Handguns 1952 (Box 50)
  - Vieux Carre Civic Association 1953 (Box 50)
  - Virginia Players - Letter from the Johnstons n.d. (Box 50)
  - Wake Island 1958 (Box 50)
  - Washington Crossing n.d. (Box 50)
  - Washington, D.C. - Problems 1958-1959 (Box 50)
  - Water Pollution 1955, 1956 (Box 50)
  - WCTV - Research 1965, n.d. (Box 51)
  - Weinger, Murray (Copa in Florida) 1955 (Box 51)
  - Welsh, Miriam 1967-1968 (Box 51)
  - "We Went Fishing!" 1960 (Box 51)
  - Whiplash (False Insurance Claims) 1957-1958 (Box 51)
  - Wildcatting (Thomas Walker Murray) 1958-1959 (Box 51)
  - Wilkinson, Bud 1956 (Box 51)
  - Wilkinson, Buzzy 1954 (Box 51)
  - Williamsburg - Jamestown 1956 (Box 51)
  - "Wings Across the World" 1966-1969 (Box 51)
  - Winterhalter, Hugo 1952 (Box 52)
  - Wolfsohn, Venlo - "This Guinea Pig is Dying" 1961-1963 (Box 52)
  - Wood, Buck (C & O Fireman) 1954 (Box 52)
  - Wood, H.P. - Estate 1953 (Box 52)
  - YMCA - President's Material 1966-1967 (Box 52)
  - Young, Buddy 1952-1953 (Box 52)
  - Young, Robert 1953-1954 (Box 52)
  - Young Men Can Change the World 1959-1971, 2 folders (Box 52)
  - Young Men Can Change the World 1959-1971, 4 folders (Box 53)
  - "You've Got to be a Little Bit Nuts to be a Professional Football Quarterback" - Correspondence, Research, Manuscript 1957 (Box 53)
  - Zaharias, Babe 1953 (Box 53)
- Miscellaneous Articles & Stories (Box 53-56)
  - Fiction and Articles Sold n.d. (Box 53)
  - Fiction and Articles Sold n.d. (Box 54)
  - Rejected Manuscripts (Not Dead) n.d., 3 folders (Box 54)
  - Rejected Manuscripts n.d. (Box 54)
  - Rejected Manuscripts n.d., 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Rejected Fiction, 1947-1948 1946-1948, n.d., 3 folders (Box 55)
  - Rejected Fiction 1960, n.d., 3 folders (Box 56)
  - Fiction ca. 1942-1943 (Box 56)
  - Unpublished Fiction n.d. (Box 56)